Anne Martindell Papers, 1898-2008 (bulk 1968-1990): Finding Aid MC203
Public Policy Papers
Anne Martindell Papers
1898-2008
1968-1990
Public Policy Papers
Martindell, Anne Clark, 1914-2008
MC203
32 boxes
Anne Martindell was one of the first three women to serve in the New Jersey State Senate. After her four-year term ended in 1977, she served as director of the Office for Foreign Disaster Assistance, and was ambassador to New Zealand and Western Samoa for a two-year term. The papers document her career in politics and civil service, and also contain her unpublished memoirs and personal papers.
Scope and Contents
The Anne Martindell papers document Martindell's personal and professional activities from the 1920s to the 1990s. The bulk of the collection concerns Martindell's professional career in New Jersey politics, the State Department's Office of Foreign Disaster Assistance, and as ambassador to New Zealand and Western Samoa. There is little material related to the United States-New Zealand Council, which Martindell helped to found.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open for research.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
This collection contains materials acquired from a Zip Disk. Researchers are responsible for meeting the technical requirements needed to access these materials, including any and all hardware and software.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Received in 2003. Accession records associated with this collection are ML.2003.017 and ML.2006.003.
An accrual of one box of papers was received from Roger Martindell in February, 2019 (ML.2019.007).
Appraisal
Duplicates, personal material, and documents of little evidential or information value were separated from the collection and returned to Ms. Martindell's family.
Accruals
No accruals are expected.
Martindell, Anne Clark, 1914-2008
Biographical / Historical
Anne Clark Martindell was born in New York City's Park Plaza Hotel on July 18, 1914. She attended boarding school in Maryland and enrolled at Smith College in 1932. After her first year at Smith, Martindell's father insisted that she return home, maintaining that no man would want to marry an educated woman. (Martindell, who had wanted to go on to law school, would later return to Smith College and earn her bachelor's degree in the class of 2002, at the age of 87. She was also awarded an honorary Doctor of Laws degree.) After leaving Smith, Martindell married George Scott, with whom she had three children. Martindell divorced Scott after thirteen years of marriage. She later married Jackson Martindell, owner of the Who's Who publications, and had a son.
Martindell was in her fifties when she first became active in politics. She attended the 1968 Democratic Convention in Chicago in support of Senate candidate Eugene McCarthy, where she observed the violence against protesters of the Vietnam War. Shortly thereafter, she was invited to become vice-chair of the New Jersey Democratic Party. After four years in that post, Martindell was encouraged to run for the state senate seat in predominantly Republican Mercer County, and after an unexpected victory she spent her four-year term concentrating on women's issues, education, and the environment. While in the state senate, she served as chair of the Education Committee, member of the Appropriations Committee, chair of the Budget Revision Subcommittee for Higher Education, chair of the Joint State Library Committee, member of the Senate Nursing Home Commission, and chair of the Committee to Defeat Casino Gambling.
Martindell attended the 1976 Democratic National Convention as a Carter delegate, and was an active voice for Jimmy Carter throughout New Jersey. After Carter's election to the presidency, Martindell was appointed to the Commission to Review Ambassadorial Appointments, and went on to become director of the Office of Foreign Disaster Assistance (OFDA), part of the State Department's Agency for International Development. In the course of her work for OFDA, she surveyed the reconstruction efforts at natural disaster sites throughout the world. This work would eventually bring her to the attention of the Ambassadorship Review Board. She was later nominated for the ambassadorship to New Zealand and Western Samoa in 1979, and served in that capacity until 1981.
During her two-year term as ambassador, Martindell traveled widely, and worked hard to improve and maintain positive relations between the U. S. and New Zealand. As the first female ambassador to New Zealand, she faced some resistance, but her persistence and personal charm endeared her to the people of New Zealand. She met New Zealand painter Tosswill Woollaston during her time as ambassador, and maintained a close relationship with him until his death in 1998.
After returning from New Zealand, Martindell retained close ties with the country, helping to found the United States-New Zealand Council in 1986. Though she continued to travel frequently, Martindell remained active in New Jersey politics as a fundraiser and donor
Politicians--New Jersey--Correspondence.; Women in politics.; Women ambassadors--New Zealand.; New Jersey politics and government 1951-.; Correspondence.; Memoirs.; Photographs.; Born digital.; United States; Carter, Jimmy, 1924-; Martindell, Anne Clark, 1914-2008
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1918-1999; 4 boxes
  Scope and Contents
  The Correspondence series documents Martindell's personal as well as professional life. The series contains family letters as well as those relating to her time in the New Jersey State Senate, State Department, and time as ambassador. There are also letters regarding her activities in New Jersey politics and as an early backer of Jimmy Carter, the head of the Women's Division of the Democratic Party, and an influential financer of campaigns. Many of the letters contain information about both her personal life and her career and political activities. Of special note are folders of letters from Jimmy Carter, Walter Mondale, and Frank Thompson. Additionally there are letters from Bill Bradley, Brendan T. Byrne, Robert Torricelli, Ronald Reagan, and Gary Hart.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Agency for International Development, 1977-1983; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ambassadorial, 1979; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bradley, Bill, 1993; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Byrne, Brendan T, 1977; 1982; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Campaign, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Carter Administration, 1977; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Carter, Jimmy, 1982; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Center for National Policy, 1990; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Commission on Ambassadorial Appointments, 1977; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Congratulations and Thank You - Senate Campaign, 1973; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1972; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Distinguished People, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 12)
    includes letters from Gary Hart, Walter Mondale, and Ronald Reagan
  - Family, 1918-1983; 2 boxes
    - Clark, Blair, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Clark, Mrs. Blair, 1918-1919 circa 1930, 5 folders (Box 1, Folder 14-18)
    - Dearest Family Letters, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Family, 1969-1983; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Gore, Albert, 1992; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Hughes, Richard J, 1979; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - IRS Inquiry, 1975; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Legislative, 1971-1977; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Maita, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Mondale, Walter, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - New Zealand, 1984-1986; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - North Country School, 1963-1983; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Political, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Position Inquiries, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Rutgers University, 1984; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Scott, George, 1945-1971; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Senate, 1974-1975; 1 box
    - General, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Staff, 1974; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Thank You Letters, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Thompson, Frank, 1967-1975; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Torricelli, Robert, 1987; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Wellington Letters, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Woollaston, Toss, 1980s-1990s; 5 folders (Box 3, Folder 7-11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958-1997 and undated, 6 folders (Box 4, Folder 1-6)
- Series 2: Professional and Political Career, 1968-1993 and undated, 1963-2000; 16 boxes
  The Professional and Political Career series documents Martindell's career, including her time in the New Jersey State Senate, as director of the Office of Foreign Disaster Assistance, as ambassador to New Zealand and Western Samoa, as well as her involvement with New Jersey Democratic Party and the Carter campaign. The series includes statements, speeches, correspondence and other materials, and is divided into four subseries: Ambassador to New Zealand, Democratic Party, New Jersey State Senate and Subject Files.
  All subseries are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Subseries 2A: Ambassador to New Zealand and Western Samoa, 1971-1991; 3 boxes
    The New Zealand and Western Samoa subseries contains speeches, memos, and scrapbooks relating to Martindell's service as Ambassador from 1979-1981. Included are records created by the State Department's Foreign Service Institute for ambassadors, including background information on New Zealand and Western Samoa, and advice on conduct and techniques for diplomats.
    The materials in this subseries are arranged alphabetically by type of material.
    - Ambassadorial Appointment Committee, 1973; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Ambassadorial Seminar, 1979; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Background Info, 1980-1986; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Forms and Memos, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Lectures (Polynesia and U.S.-N.Z. Relationship), undated; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Oral History Interview, 1981; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Personal Finances, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Reception Book, circa 1979 (removed to Box 31), 1 box (Box 6)
    - Report on ANZUS/nuclear vessels incident, 1981-1988; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, 1991; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971-1989; 2 boxes
      - General, 1985-1989; 4 folders (Box 6, Folder 3-6)
      - Ambassadorial Files, circa 1979; 2 folders (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
      - Ambassadorial Files (continued), circa 1979 (1 folder), 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Clippings, 1971-1987; 3 folders (Box 7, Folder 2-4)
  - Subseries 2B: Democratic Party, 1963-1993; 3 boxes
    The Democratic Party subseries documents Martindell's involvement in Democratic Party politics at both the New Jersey and national levels. Materials include lists, memos, press releases, and briefing materials related to Martindell's work with Jimmy Carter, Hillary Clinton, and the George McGovern and Eugene McCarthy campaigns. Information about the 1976 Democratic National Convention and the New Jersey Democratic State Committee may also be found in the subseries.
    The materials in this subseries are arranged alphabetically by the name of people or groups Martindell was involved with in her professional life.
    - Carter, Jimmy, 1975-1976; 1 box
      - General, 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
      - Task Force to Investigate Discrimination Against Women, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Clinton, Hillary, 1992-1993; 1 box
      - General, 1993; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Fund Raising Dinner, 1992; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Contact Information, Political Groups, 1981; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1970; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Democratic State Committee, 1968-1972; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Hart, Gary, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - McCarthy Campaign, 1968; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - McGovern Campaign, 1972, dates not examined; 3 folders (Box 8, Folder 5-7)
    - Mondale Fundraising, 1979-1983; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - New Jersey, circa 1969; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - New Jersey (continued), 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Presidential Candidates, 1992; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Schroeder, Patricia, 1987; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963-1973; 3 folders (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
  - Subseries 2C: New Jersey State Senate, 1969-2000; 5 boxes
    The New Jersey State Senate subseries consists of bills, press releases, briefing materials, memos, schedules, and clippings relating to Martindell's four-year term in the New Jersey State Senate. Also included are resolutions and other material from the New Jersey Joint Appropriations Committee.
    The materials in this subseries are arranged according to type of doumentation or activity.
    - Bills, 1974-1977; 1 box
      - General, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Sponsored by Martindell, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Campaign, 1973; 1 box
      - Button, undated; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Memos, 1973; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Schedules, 1973; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Casino Gambling--No Dice, 1973-1977; 1 box (Box 32)
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      ML.2019.007
      This box contains correspondence, clippings, press releases, a public transcript hearing, etc. that relate to a 1974 referendum to change the New Jersey state constitution to permit casino gambling, as well as the "No Dice" campaign to defeat the referendum. Martindell was active in opposing the referendum, which did not pass in 1974.
    - Later Clippings on Casinos and Gambling, 1982-2000; 1 box (Box 32)
    - Education (Higher, New Jersey), 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Election (Clippings), 1973; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Joint Appropriations Committee, 1977; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Mailings, 1973; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - New Jersey Commission on Financing Post Secondary Education, 1976; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - New Jersey Legislature Bulletin and Appropriations, 1973; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Nursing Home Commission, 1974-1975; 1 box
      - General, 1974; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Nursing Home Commission Study, 1975; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases, 1973-1977; 2 folders (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
    - Resolutions, 1974-1977; 1 box
      - General, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Voting Record, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - State Committee Issues Forum, 1969; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Statements, Legislative, 1974; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Women, 1972-1976; 2 folders (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1977; 2 boxes
      - General, 1973-, circa 1975; 4 folders (Box 12, Folder 7-10)
      - Clippings, 1974-1977; 2 folders (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
      - Scrapbooks, circa 1975; 3 folders (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
  - Subseries 2D: Subject Files, 1970-1996; 7 boxes
    The Subject Files subseries consists of records related to a variety of Martindell's professional activities, and includes material from her work with the Office of Foreign Disaster Assistance, the Eagleton Institute, and the New Jersey Institute on Conflict Resolution and Peace Studies. Also included are files regarding her lawsuit against the International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation (ITT); Martindell sued ITT due to their misuse of company funds for political purposes in a foreign country.
    The materilas in this subseries are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Apgar Award, 1993 (certificate removed to Box 31), 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Congressional Testimony, circa 1985; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Department of State Telegrams, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Dugan, James, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Eagleton Institute, 1971; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Report, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT) Lawsuit, 1973; 2 boxes
      - Clippings, 1973; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Legal Documents, 1973; 2 folders (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
      - Legal Documents (continued), 1973; 2 folders (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1973; 3 folders (Box 15, Folder 3-5)
    - Meyner, Helen, 1972; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO), circa 1985; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - New Jersey Institute on Conflict Resolution and Peace Studies, 1984-1987 (1 folder), 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - New Jersey Institute on Conflict Resolution and Peace Studies (continued), 1984-1987 (1 folder), 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Nuclear Weapons, circa 1983; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Office of Foreign Disaster Assistance (OFDA), 1977-1981; 1 box
      - General, circa 1977-1981; 5 folders (Box 16, Folder 3-7)
      - Clippings, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Partners for Peace, circa 1977; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Prison Case Work, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Publicity Clippings, 1971-1992; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Queen's Service Order, 1990; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Conference, 1983; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, 1972-1994; 2 folders (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
    - Speeches (continued), 1972-1994; 2 folders (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - State Department, 1977; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Statements, undated; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Thompson, Frank, 1970; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Watergate, circa 1973; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Welfare, undated; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Women, 1972-1996; 2 boxes
      - General, 1972-1996 (1 folder), 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - General (continued), 1972-1996; 2 folders (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
      - Women's Committee, 1981-1986; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1974 and undated, 2 folders (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings, undated; 2 folders (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
- Series 3: Memoirs, 1898-1997 and undated, 8 boxes
  The Memoirs series consists of Martindell's source material, notes, and drafts relating to the unpublished autobiography that she wrote in the late 1990s. These documents were moved by Martindell, during the writing process, to their present arrangement from elsewhere within her own files. Materials range from family information from the late 19th century to records documenting Martindell's political activities in the late 1980s. This series is divided into two subseries: Chapter Files and Subject Files
  The materials in this series are arranged into Chapter files and Subject files.
  - Subseries 3A: Chapter Files, 1898-1995; 7 boxes
    The Chapter Files subseries includes drafts, notes and a substantial amount of source material relating to Martindell's unpublished autobiography. The subseries is arranged by chapter number, and chapter titles indicate the subject of each section of the book. Researchers should note that these files contain a small amount of photographs in addition to those found in the Photographs series.
    Arranged by chapter number.
    - Chapter 3: Beginnings, 1990-1992; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Chapter 4: Nanny, 1994; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Chapter 5: The Blairs, 1898-1985; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Chapter 6: The Clarks, 1970-1989; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Chapter 8: School Days, 1991; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Chapter 10: Door Slams Shut, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Chapter 11: The War, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Chapter 13: Innkeepers, 1978-1995; 2 folders (Box 20, Folder 8-9)
    - Chapter 15: Remarriage, 1950-1986; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Chapter 16: Tall Tales From Texas, 1955-1960; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Chapter 18: North Country School, 1980-1992; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Chapter 19: City of God, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Chapter 20: Rx - The Door Opens, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Chapter 21: McCarthy Campaign, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Chapter 22: Chicago 1968 circa 1968, 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Chapter 23: Party Discipline, 1969-1971; 2 folders (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
    - Chapter 24: Organizing New Jersey, 1969-1972; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Chapter 25: George McGovern Campaign, 1970-1972; 2 folders (Box 22, Folder 2-3)
    - Chapter 26: Chairman of the Delegation/Running for Office, 1970-1972; 1995; 2 folders (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
      (oversize correspondence removed to Box 31)
    - Chapter 27: A Woman in Office/Running for Office, 1969-1975; 2 folders (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
    - Chapter 28: Casinos - No Dice, 1974; 2 folders (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
    - Chapter 29: Taxes, Taxes, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Chapter 30: Carter/Why Not the Best?, 1975-1989; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Chapter 30: Carter/Why Not the Best? (continued), 1975-1989; 2 folders (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
    - Chapter 31: Foreign Disaster Office/Disaster Relief, 1977-1980; 4 folders (Box 24, Folder 3-6)
    - Chapter 32: Ambassadorial Experience and Plan, circa 1980; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Chapter 33: Wellington, 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
    - Chapter 34: Samoan Tales, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Chapter 35: Antarctica, 1979; 2 folders (Box 25, Folder 5-6)
    - Chapter 36: The Pacific Way, 1979-1987; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Chapter 37: A View From The Outside, 1980; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Chapter 38: Diplomatic Life, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Chapter 39: Farewells, 1981; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Chapter 40: Toss, 1992; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Chapter 31, 32, 33, 35, circa 1980), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 3B: Subject Files, 1968-1997; 2 boxes
    The Subject Files subseries, like the Chapter Files subseries, contains drafts, notes and source material relating to Martindell's unpublished autobiography. Martindell filed this material separately from the material in the Chapter Files. It has been arranged alphabetically by subject. This subseries also documents the editorial process and Martindell's inquiries regarding publication.
    - Ambassador to New Zealand, 1978-1983; 2 boxes
      - General, 1978-1983; 2 folders (Box 26, Folder 7-8)
      - Australia-New Zealand-United States Treaty (ANZUS) Trip, 1979; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Salary and Financial Information, 1979; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1983-1991; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1997; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Diary, undated; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Drafts, undated; 2 folders (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
    - Expenses, 1990-1992; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Publication, 1989-1992; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968-1995 and undated, 4 folders (Box 27, Folder 10-13)
- Series 4: Subject Files, 1923-2008; 4 boxes